来讨论美国最持久的战争
debating America's longest war
你和我都知道  他们只知道
when you know as well as I know that they know
他们手里讲话要点里的那点东西
exactly as much as what's printed in their talking points?
那你想请谁来
Who would you have preferred?
企业研究所  布鲁金斯研究所
Anybody from AEI, Brookings,
传统基金会  卡托研究所的人
Heritage, Cato.
国务院或者国防部的人
Anybody from State or Defense.
众议院或者参议院外交关系委员会的人
Anybody from House or Senate Foreign Relations.
最起码也要请
At the very least you could get the guy
实际上写那些谈话要点的人来啊
who wrote the talking points.
中期选举马上要开始了
There's a midterm election coming up.
还有六个月呢
In six months.
你到底为什么要请红蓝两个阵营的人
So why do you book a red guy and a blue guy?